Inventory of the Tibor Flórián papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Oversize materials, circa 1926-1978 (Box 110)
  - Honorary diplomas and plaques
    Associatio Alumnorum Scholarum Piarum Hungariae, Zrínyi Miklós Literary Circle, Árpád Academy, Magyar Kongresszus, Two Thousand Men of Achievement, International PEN, American Biographical Institute, and others.
  - Group photograph of a school sports team, 1926
  - Reproduction of a photograph of Cardinal József Mindszenty
  - Poems by Flórián, A Single Spark and Rigófészek, illustrated by Barbara Shenkman
  - Hand-drawn map of Hungary entitled "Collectivization in Hungary: 7/1954"
  - Newspaper articles on the Hungarian 1956 revolution in American press
  - Promotional materials